https://www.intersafe.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Our Services
Fixed Wire Testing (EICR)
Our Services
Fixed Wire Testing (EICR)
Privacy Policy
Intersafe are independently owned electrical compliance specialists, offering PAT Testing, Fixed Wire Testing and Remedials, Emergency Light Testing and LED Installations.
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, www.intersafe.co.uk will be referred to as the Intersafe website and www.fixedtesting.com will be referred to as the Fixed Testing website. How We Collect DataWe collect certain information or data about you when you use the Intersafe website and the Fixed Testing website.If you contact us with questions, queries or feedback using our online quote or contact forms, live chat or by sending us an email, you will provide us with your name and contact details including your email address.When you visit our website, we use a 3rd party tool, Google Analytics, which can identify your IP address and details of which web browser you used to access our site. We use the information in Google Analytics to understand how website visitors use our website, in order for us to improve our website experience.
We do not, nor allow Google Analytics to, make any effort to identify individuals from this data.We also use a third party cookie, called _lfuuid. The cookie is accepted or declined by selecting the relevant option in the consent banner that will appear upon your first visit to our website. The cookie allows a website to track visitor behavior on the sites on which the cookie is installed. Tracking is performed anonymously unless a user identifies himself by submitting a form. The cookie is persistent for 10 years before it expires.What Data We Store & How We Use ItWe record and store your business or organisation name, business type and address. We hold your name, job title, company email address and company telephone number. This is held in our database, hosted on our secure server.We will use your data in order to respond to any queries your raise or to deliver the services you have requested. If we complete electrical inspection or testing or LED installation, we will also record contact details for your finance / accounts payable team. We will use your data to arrange site surveys, send you electrical inspection reports, remind you when a retest is due and any other aspects of service delivery.
If you do not already contract us, we will use your details to contact you ahead of your renewal date by processing your data on the basis of legitimate interest. If you agree to provide us with your email address we will add you to our 6-weekly newsletter. You can unsubscribe at any time using the unsubscribe link in the email. Alternatively you can email info@intersafe.co.uk or write to Intersafe Ltd, Unit 5 Old Farm Court, Nursling Street, Southampton SO16 0AJ.Keeping your data secureWhilst we cannot guarantee the security of any data you submit over the internet, we do have procedures and security features in place to try and keep your data secure once we receive it.Disclosing your informationWe won't share your information with any other organisations for marketing, market research or commercial purposes, and we don't pass on your details to other websites for their own usage. We do use reputable 3rd party data processors, such as our email sending platform. We may pass on your personal information if we have a legal obligation to do so, or if we have to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements.Your RightsYou have the right to know what information we hold about you, and you can request a copy of this at any time by contacting us. If you find details to be incorrect or out of date, you may ask us to correct them. You also have the right to ask us to remove all of your contact details sand to not contact you in future for marketing purposes.
You can email us at info@intersafe.co.uk, call us on 02380 236200 or write to us at Unit 5 Old Farm Court, Nursling Street, Southampton SO16 0AJ.Even if you ask us to remove your contact details from marketing activities, we may still contact you regarding your account, or services which we are contractually bound to deliver.Links to other websitesThe Intersafe website contains links to and from other websites.This privacy policy only applies to this website and fixed testing.com (both owned by Intersafe), and doesn't cover other websites and organisations that we may link to.If you go to another website from this one, read the privacy policy on that website to find out what it does with your information.Last updated 7 July 2020
